{
  "Presentacion":
  {
    "Titulo":"Drag and Drop",
    "Descripcion":"Definitely, the best option for the job is John Brown, but he will have to adapt to the schedules at the office. Help me organize his routine activities in a logical order. Drag the activities to the blank spaces."
  },
  "Actividad":
  [
   
    {
      "Pregunta":"to abide",
      "Respuesta":"1"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"abode",
      "Respuesta":"2"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"abode past",
      "Respuesta":"3"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"to arise",
      "Respuesta":"4"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"arose",
      "Respuesta":"5"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"arisen",
      "Respuesta":"6"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"to awake",
      "Respuesta":"7"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"awoke",
      "Respuesta":"8"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"awoken",
      "Respuesta":"9"
    },
    {
      "Pregunta":"to bear",
      "Respuesta":"10"
    }

  ],
  "Enunciado" :[
    {
      "Item":"audio/act10/01.mp3"
    },
    {
      "Item":"audio/act10/02.mp3"
    },
    {
      "Item":"audio/act10/03.mp3"
    },
    {
      "Item":"audio/act10/04.mp3"
    },
    {
      "Item":"audio/act10/05.mp3"
    },
    {
      "Item":"audio/act10/06.mp3"
    },
    {
      "Item":"audio/act10/07.mp3"
    },
    {
      "Item":"audio/act10/08.mp3"
    },
    {
      "Item":"audio/act10/09.mp3"
    },
    {
      "Item":"audio/act10/10.mp3"
    }
  ],    
  "Retroalimentacion":
  {
    "Bien":"Excellent! You can now identify the main actions of Johnâ€™s routine. Is yours similar?",
    "Mal":"Try again! Think about your own routine. It must not be too different from yours."
  },
 "Botones":
 {
    "limpiar":"Clear",
    "enviar":"Send",
    "siguiente":"Next",
    "repetir":"Re"
 }
}